<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>automatic export on Better BibTeX for Zotero</title>
    <link>/zotero-better-bibtex/tags/automatic-export/</link>
    <description>Recent content in automatic export on Better BibTeX for Zotero</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/zotero-better-bibtex/tags/automatic-export/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Automatic export</title>
      <link>/zotero-better-bibtex/exporting/auto/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/zotero-better-bibtex/exporting/auto/</guid>
      <description>When exporting using BBT (by right-clicking on &amp;lsquo;my library&amp;rsquo; from the main window of Zotero) you will be offered a new export option: Keep updated. Checking this option registers the export for automation; any changes to the collection or library you exported after you&amp;rsquo;ve completed the current export will trigger an automatic re-export to update the bib file. You can review/remove exports from the BBT preferences. While I&amp;rsquo;ve gone to some lengths to make sure performance is OK, don&amp;rsquo;t go overboard with the number of auto-exports you have going.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Export</title>
      <link>/zotero-better-bibtex/installation/preferences/export/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/zotero-better-bibtex/installation/preferences/export/</guid>
      <description>The Better BibTeX Configuration can be found under the regular Zotero preferences pane, tab &amp;lsquo;Better BibTeX&amp;rsquo;.
The configuration of Better BibTeX is a little baroque compared to the standard Zotero Bib(La)TeX exporters (which only have hidden preferences). The defaults should just work, but here&amp;rsquo;s an attempt to describe what they do.
Making any change here will drop your entire export cache. This is usually not a problem unless you have a really large library, but you can read about what is involved here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>